It's time for Enjoy Simple English
今年度からナビゲーターを務める森崎ウィンです
2024年度毎週火曜日は短編のショートコメディー
Comedy Sketchesをお届けします
今日はスーツ店にワイシャツを探しに来た男性の話
転校を繰り返す生徒の話
この2本でございます
早速聞いてみましょう
拍手
スーツショップ
That sounds great. Then, I'd like to buy a white cotton shirt, please.
Great. One moment, please.
There should be one your size here.
If you don't have one, then...
No, no, no, no. Please wait. I know there is one here.
Aha! Here you go. A pair of suspenders.
they're in fashion you know
i don't need suspenders i wear belts
oh i see
where is that shirt
aha
did you find it
here's a rainbow color necktie
the colors will look great on a white shirt
i'm not looking for neckties either
can you please find the white shirt
I want a shirt just like the one you are wearing.
Why didn't you say so?
Wait a minute, please.
Why are you taking off your shirt?
You said you wanted this shirt.
I want that type of shirt, but a new one.
Oh, I'm sorry, but they're all sold out.
新しい学生をお迎えします
おはようございます
新しい友人をお迎えします
田中さん、ご紹介をお願いいたします
こんにちは、田中信一です
私は日本から来ています
初めて会いました
田中さん、どのくらい前に日本に住んでいたのですか?
2ヶ月です
That's not very long.
Before Germany, I lived in Italy. Gelato is very buono.
I see. How long were you in Italy?
The same as Germany, two months. I want to make lots of new amigos.
Amigos? Did you also live in Spain?
I did.
Wow! You have lived in many countries, haven't you?
Yes, my father's hobby is moving, so we move every two months.
That's quite a lot.
Obrigado, shukuran, tak.
That's thank you in Portuguese, Arabic and Swedish.
Wow, but why did you say thank you?
I always learn how to say thank you in a new language
That makes sense
By the way, did you also live in Mexico, Scotland, Texas and
うずまさきょうと
I did! How did you know?
Well, you're wearing a colorful poncho, a kilt, cowboy boots
and your hair is in the samurai chonmage style
いやーこのコメディは面白い
ドレスシャツこれYシャツのこと言うんですね実は僕も知らなかったです
あとインフェッション今流行ってる言いたかったら
It's in fashion僕これ聞いてからもうれんこしております
それではI hope to see you tomorrow